{
    "subject": "Grand_Empress_Dowager_Shangguan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Emperor_Zhao_of_Han",
    "human_readable": "Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan is married to Emperor Zhao of Han.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9825777411460876,
            "question": "Who was the Emperor who was married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9751670956611633,
            "question": "Name the empress who was married to Emperor Zhao of Han."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.970858097076416,
            "question": "What is the name of the emperor married to Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9624412655830383,
            "question": "To whom was Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9578399658203125,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan and Emperor Zhao of Han?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9258900284767151,
            "question": "Who was Emperor Zhao of Han married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7772807478904724,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the historical period in which Emperor Zhao of Han and Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan lived?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5131025314331055,
            "question": "Is Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan known for her political influence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34578239917755127,
            "question": "What were some key events during Emperor Zhao of Han's reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29993996024131775,
            "question": "What title did Shangguan hold?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan is married to Emperor Zhao of Han.",
            "html": "yago_30246_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some key events during Emperor Zhao of Han's reign?",
            "html": "yago_30246_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan known for her political influence?",
            "html": "yago_30246_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the historical period in which Emperor Zhao of Han and Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan lived?",
            "html": "yago_30246_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30246_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The information in the documents supports that Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan was indeed married to Emperor Zhao of Han. This can be seen in multiple files (5.txt, 27.txt, and others) where it is stated that she was an Empress, Empress Dowager, and Grand Empress Dowager during the Han Dynasty and wife to Emperor Zhao."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Grand Empress Dowager Shangguan was indeed the wife of Emperor Zhao, stating explicitly or through context (such as referring to her as an \"Empress\" and \"wife\") in several entries."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}